Who everyone looks at first
X-Engineer
I flick up before they speak
Permission
Dressed is just being me
The action's trained
And I'm in this game
And gets rearranged quick
You learn confederation
Neon smoke rising from the ruins of yesterday
They thought the fire would consume me
We slept alone in a city
Like a mist turned to dust
My sleep
Concealed a dream
Before I knew that I was already inside, they whispered my name.
In initiation, that fracture turned divine.
Silence between word, the skin, lost within.
They said don't leave me.
They said don't.
Intention in the eye became a strange relief.
Late night messages like angels, unexpected hands,
would ride time.
The darkness spoke in ancient moves.
I don't know what you are saying, I don't know what you are saying, I don't know what
you are saying, I don't know what you are saying, I don't know what you are saying, I don't
pruta jagatra ya vajra deha vajra pujha vajra kaya vajra thunda
vajra mukha vajra nakha vajra vahu vajra roma vajra netra vajra danta vajra sharir
sakal atma kaya bheemakar pinga laaksh ugr pralayakala rodra veera vajra vata
dashgriva krutanta sita vishwasa isvara putra anjanagadha sambhuta
udaya bhaskar vimbha nal agrasak devadana varshimuni vande
pashupatastra brahmastra bailavastra nara nastra kala shakti kastra dhanda kastra
pashagha rastra nivarana pashupatastra brahmastra bailavastra nara
Sarva Shakti Grasana Mamatma Raksha Dhyani Varan Raksha Kha
Vedasiddha Sthir Kaal Agni Niraha Darsana Lakshmana Praana Pratishtha Nanda Kara
Bhajala Agni Marma Bhedin Sarva Shatron Chindi Chindi Mamavairana
Khadaya Khasana Jeevan Parvatothi Dhvansana
Sugriva Sakhyakarna Nishkalanka Kumar Brahmacharin
I've been thinking about it for a long time, I've been thinking about it for a long time, I've been thinking about it for a long time, I've been thinking about it for a long time, I've been thinking about it for a long time, I've been thinking about it for a long time, I've been thinking about it for a long time, I've been thinking about it for a long time, I've been thinking about it for a long time, I've been thinking about it for a long time, I've been thinking about it for a long time, I've been thinking about it for a long time, I've been thinking about it for a long time, I've been thinking about it for a long time, I've been thinking about it for a long time, I've been thinking about it for a long time, I've been thinking about it for a long time, I've been thinking about it for a long time, I've been thinking about it for a long time, I've been thinking about it for a long time, I've been
Katsvar, Visham Katsvar, Sheet Katsvar, Ekahi Katsvar, Yahi Katsvar, Traihi Katsvar, Chaturthamasi Katsvar, Masi Katsvar, Sanmasi Katsvar, Samatsari Katsvar, Astyantarga Katsvar, Mahapasma, Rashramika Pasma, Ramshabhedaya Bhedaya, Akshishula, Sherashula, Darshula, Karthik, Darshula, Darshula, Darshula, Darshula, Darshula, Darshula, Darshula, Darshula, Darshula, Darshula, Darshula, Darshula, Darshula, Darshula, Darshula, Darshula, Darshula, Darshula, Darshula, Darshula, Darshula, Darshula
Shoola, Netra Shoola, Buddha Shoola, Kachi Shoola, Janu Shoola, Jangha Shoola, Hastha Shoola, Baada Shoola, Gulva Shoola, Vaata Shoola, Itta Shoola, Baayu Shoola, Stana Shoola, Parinama Shoola, Paridhama Shoola, Paribhana Shoola, Danta Shoola, Kukshi Shoola, Sumanash Shoola, Sarva Shoolaani, Nirmoolaya, Nirmukakshasakko, Paashana, Sukhi Takshaka, Kajgala, Roa, Paashal, Kajgala, Paridhama Shoola, Paridhama Shoola, Paridhama Shoola, Paridhama Shoola, Paridhama Shoola, Paridhama Shoola, Paridhama Shoola,
In the name of the Lord, the most Gracious, the most Merciful, the most Merciful, the most Merciful, the most Merciful, the most Merciful, the most Merciful, the most Merciful, the most Merciful, the most Merciful, the most Merciful, the most Merciful, the most Merciful, the most Merciful, the most Merciful, the most Merciful, the most Merciful, the most Merciful, the most Merciful, the most Merciful, the most Merciful, the most Merciful, the most Merciful, the most Merciful, the most Merciful, the most Merciful, the most Merciful, the most Merciful, the most Merciful, the most Merciful, the most Merciful, the most Merciful, the most Merciful, the most Merciful, the most Merciful, the most Merciful, the most Merciful, the most Merciful, the most Merciful, the most Merciful, the most Merciful, the most Merciful, the most Merciful, the
Mamaprasadam Kuru Kuru Mamaprasannashree Ramasheva Kasimha Bhairava Swaroop
Mam Raksha Raksha Om Ram Reem Guru Ram Reem
Kashmoh Brahm Shraam Shreem Kram Kreem Kram Kreem
Ram Reem Guru Reim Ram Ruh Ram Reem
Kha Kha Jai Jai Maaranam Rnagur Nandam
Ram Reem Guru Fathe Ghe Ghe Swaha
Anum De Prasahasam Adhaya Prasaya Sahaya
Vashya, Vashya, Vashya, Shyamaya, Shyamaya, Astra, Trishuladamaru, Khadga, Kala, Mritya, Yuppa, Tabhushana, Paramantra, Parayantra, Paratantra, Satas, Astra, Koti, Tejah, Pungadasha, Kula, Vishchakana, Megadasha, Lutana, Vishamhana, Hansar, Vavisham, Bandhaya, Bandhaya, Vazra, Tundu, Uchata, Vaishana, Yudha, Dharaka, Marma, Vibandhaya, Bandhaya, Vasine, Atipur, Vashaktaya.
Sarvayudhadaraya Swaha Akshayaya Ghe Ghe Ghe Ghe Om Lallallam Grand Grand Swaha Om Hamleem Loom Pat Ghe Ghe Swaha Om Shran Shreem Shreem Shreem Shran Shreem Om Namo Bhagavate Bhadra Zati Ekata Rudravi Rahanumate
Brahma Swarupa Dasha Dishnu Rupa Ekadasha Rudrava Tara Dvaadasha Arka Tejahatra Yodasha
Somamukh Veera Hanumanstha Tambhinimohini Vashi Karinitantraika Saapadava Nagarraaja Mukha
Bandha Nabala Mukha Makara Mukha Singha Mukha Jihwa Mukhaani Bandha Ya Bandha Ya Stambha
Ya Stambha Ya Vyagra Mukha Sarva Rishchika Gani
Jvalavisham nirgamaya nirgamaya sarvajan vairimukam bandhaya bandhaya papahar vi rahanum anishvarataar vayunandana anjanaasuta bandhaya bandhaya shri rama chandraseghaka
Ram, Ram, Ram, Aasaya, Aasaya, Aalim, Lam, Grim, Cream, Yam, Bhai, Mram, Ra, Hath, Hath, Khad, Khad, Sarvajan, Vishvajan, Shadrujan, Vashyajan, Sarvajan, Siddhusham, Lam, Lam, Sreem, Ram, He, Man, Stambhaya, Stambhaya, Bhanjaya, Bhanjaya, Adri, Reem, Vaheem, He, Me, Sarvaheem, Sagar, He, He, Vam, Vam, Sarvam, Mantra, Tha, Thar, Vana, Veda, Siddhik, Kuru, Kuru, Swaha, Sriram, Achandra, Vahacham, Vahacham, Vahacham, Vahacham, Vahacham, Vahacham, Vahacham,
Srimahadeva Vajra, Srivira Bhadrastha Vajra, Trisandhyam Yahpathennara, Vedya Vanishad Sampo,
O Asasriya Tharvana Bhadrakali Uggra Krityabhagavati, Pratyangi Rambha Parmeshwari Mahamantrasya.
Bhairavaroshi, Anushnu Chanda, Devi Gayatri Chanda, Atharvana Bhadrakali, Ugra Kritya Bhagavati, Pratyangi, Amma, Parameshwari, Devata, Shambhiji, Shri Shatthi, Hapat, Kilak, Mamma, Atharvana Bhadrakali, Ugra Kritya Bhagavati, Pratyangi, Amma, Parameshwari, Devata, Shambhiji, Shri Shatthi, Hapat, Kilak, Mamma, Atharvana Bhadrakali, Ugra Kritya Bhagavati, Pratyangi, Amma, Parameshwari, Devata, Shambhiji, Shri Shatthi, Devata, Shambhiji, Shri Shatthi, Devata, Shambhiji, Shri Shatthi, Devata, Shambhiji, Shri Shatthi, Devata, Shamb
Shambhijaya Namah Ghoi Hei Shaktayaya
What kill kaayana?
Rattyangir me swaree devata
Ritya rathe zape bini ho gaya
Thirishya din yasa
Shaan kushthaha shreeta
Thirase swam trinayana
Bhasitam simha vaktrodha keshin
Shoolamandam chasar pandam
Arugujayutam kuntavan
Yugradamstram
Ratkeshvalidayuktam
Urad Anil Savitri Gayatri Yukta
Yaya Pratyangi Ramam Rippu
Vidra Na Yatmika Dham Samar
Aakai Pooja Deepam Darshayami
Amma Mritatmika Pratam Mahane
San Sarvatmika Ema Mahadeva
Karunam Pratyangi
Achaṁ rukmantrasya swaroopakam jagan mangalam nāma prasiddhambhuvanatraya
sarvarakṣākaraṁ ranaṁ rahasyaṁ apitānvada
Ishwarovashinukalyani vadayamika vachamsatru-nigraham parpreksitakarmapitatrasalyadi-bhaksana maha-vijarashamanam sarvakad-pradam-dhranam
Thank you very much.
dham dham dham sridham punyadham papanashanam
Vijaya Pradam Mahārāja Jñāmī Sheshāsthatru-nāshanam
Sarvarakṣākaram Shunyagraha-pīrāvināshanam
Namastasthadam shodasham
ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ ॐ
Thank you very much.
karmār jñā pujjā prathyaṁ gīrāṁ śivaṁ
vratta-dīśbhe samāhatchakam vacham japa māvatīpa
shakattakham ātrenu sarva-śatru-vinashyati
śatra-vashchaklāyam tatasya-garśa-māmātratā
kavacham ārambham māsa-mātraṁ japa-deva sarva-śatru-vinashyati
Yama kalpayanti purvadisham rakshet kali sa atharvani
Rakshet karna vatyag ne yam sadamaam simha vahinim
Yama yam disham sadarakshet kshambhaksha jwala rupini
Nairuttyam rakshatu sadamaasman mrukshe rantar aaja
Vaya Vyam tu tada rakshet sarvam chapa tu danya taha
Dhamstra karal avadana kauberyaam vatavanala
Isanya me sada rakshet virams tyasya nebarhana
Uggra Rakshet Adho Bhage Maya Mantra Swaroopini
Urdvam Kapalini Rakshet Kshambri Hum Fatshwaroopini
Palyaat Sarvadisham Rakshet Kuru Kulla Yavirodini
Diprachitta Sada Rakshet Diwaratram Dishonisham
kuru kulya pi me putran bharyaam
harta bandhyaan me ug garu peeni
prabha jipta agraham rakshet mata
pitrur swamat rujan
shaganyaan me sadha
payat palikaan me pashoon sadha
jale rakshet krishnavasi sthale simhasanesthita
sahasravadana kshapayan me kannika sadha ajitame shiro rakshet aparajitakamada
kesan rakshet sahasrani trinitra kaal ratrika falampatumaha kroor pingdakeshi shiro ruhha
You are the one who is the one who is the one who is the one who is the one who is the one
who is the one who is the one who is the one who is the one who is the one who is the one
kapolam me sadāpātubra ghaschāpase dhire
purdham oshtaṁ sadāpāturatha sevavibhurthidha
adharostam pātumam āryātastisayam janā
dantapan tidvayam pātubram harūpi garālinī
vācam bhāgīśvari rakṣetrasanām jananī mamā
Chubhukam Patu me Indrani Tanobhir Uchha Swahelita
Karnasthanam Mam Sada Rakshatam Kambhukandhara
Kantha Dhvani Sada Patu Nadab Brahma Maimama
Jathram Tangira Putri me Vaksha Patu Kimchana
Patu me Buja Yormulam Jatvedaswarupin
dakshinam me bhujampatu sattam kala rathrika
vama bhujam vama keshi payan me parvaha tu